#### **SUMMARY**

I am a highly motivated individual who over the past 9+ years has developed an extensive pool of skill sets that I've utilized in most of my job responsibilities. I am a life-long learner, a problem solver, love to be challenged, and not afraid of tackling something new and exciting.

#### **EDUCATION**

**BFA: STUDIO ART: NEW MEDIA** 

UNIVERSITY OF NORTH TEXAS - 2003-2009

#### SKILLS

• ORGANIZATION • WEB DEVELOPMENT • WRITTEN & VERBAL • COMMUNICATION • STRONG WORK-ETHIC • TIME MANAGEMENT • CREATIVE IDEATION

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### ANSIRA/SQ1 | SR. UI/UX DEVELOPER

MARCH 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2017

Responsible for development of HTML5 banner ads, landing pages, websites, website maintenance, and e-mail template development. Also, responsible for managing and developing animated UI elements for websites and web products such as logos, icons, and interactive visuals using JavaScript and, or, CSS. Collaborating with the creative team to develop solutions that are technologically feasible in terms of animation, functionality and interactivity.

#### Other responsibilities:

- Maintaining photo studio and taking photos for internal projects, client RFPs, and website use.
- · Creating animated storyboards in After Effects for client presentations.

### ANSIRA/SQ1 | SR. MOTION GRAPHIC DESIGNER

JAN 2016 - MARCH 2017

#### Responsibilities:

- Managing Digital Studio department which handled all video, photography, and display ad projects.
- Owned all video projects for agency as a whole.
- Managed hired help for video projects.
- Built estimates for all video and display ad projects.
- Owned all Display Ad development and animation for 10+ clients.
- · Quality Control of all assets to ensure all adhere to display ad requirements.
- Working with Media Team to help facilitate trafficking process.
- Developed prototype animations for display ads and websites.
- · Managed freelance help for display ad work.
- · Collaborated with Creative team to provide conceptual input.
- Video editing and producing for internal promotional videos and client work including Instagram video and conceptual work.

## SQ1 | SR. INTERACTIVE DEVELOPER

APRIL 2012 - JAN 2016

# Responsibilities:

- Owned all display Ad production for 10+ clients.
- · Facilitated the trafficking process with Media Team.
- Managed freelance help for display ad work.
- Built Dynamic Ad process for use across current and future clients.
- Developed current HTML5 Ad Templates for use across all projects.